What's going on?
왜 그래?
My eye is a little itchy.
눈이 좀 가려워서
나도 그러네
Mine too. Yeah.
많이 충혈됐어
내 안과주치의한테 가보자
It's really red.
You should go see my eye doctor.
I'm not gonna see your ex-boyfriend.
리처드? 네 옛 애인은
보고 싶지 않아
리처드, 귀에 못 박히겠다
리처드, 리처드, 리처드
That's all I hear.
Richard, Richard, Richard.
Since we've dated,
I've said his name twice.
우리 이렇게 되고
두 번밖에 말 안 했어
알았어, 그럼
리처드, 리처드
Okay. So Richard, Richard.
It's not Richard.
It's this new guy. He's good.
리처드가 아냐
새로 온 분인데 잘 보셔
마음은 고맙지만
안과엔 가기 싫어
I'm sorry. I'm not going
to an eye doctor.
-Oh, God. Here we go.
-What?
맙소사, 또 시작이군
뭐가?
자기 눈이든 남의 눈이든
뭐가 눈 근처에 다가오면
Anytime anything comes close
to touching her eye or anyone else's...
얘는 자지러져, 이걸 봐
...she, like, freaks out. Watch.
Ross, come on!
로스! 하지 마
알았어, 나 그런 애니까
눈 얘기는 그만두자
I have a weird thing with my eye.
Can we not talk about it?
- 그래
- 알았어
Hey, Rach. You know that great song?
"Me, Myself and Eye."
너 그 명곡 알아?
나는 나
그리고 '눈'
Monica! Come on!
얘가 정말!
All those in favor
of getting lunch, say, "eye."
너희들 점심 안 먹어?
찬성하면 '눈'이라고 해
제발 그만해
Ross! Stop it!
How much did I love
The King and Eye?
내 '눈'으로 본 최고의 영화
왕과 '눈'
챈들러!
Chandler!
- 나도, 나도...
- 알았어, 제발 그만
Me too, me too!
Just stop it! That's enough!
-You okay there, man?
-Yeah. I got too excited.
너 괜찮니?
내가 미쳤지
The One with Joey's Big Break
I gotta go.
I'm taking Ben to the park.
난 벤 데리고 공원에 가야겠다
- 나 대신 뽀뽀해줘
- 그래, 안녕
-Give him a kiss for me.
-All right. Bye.
- 잘 가
- 안녕
또 보자
Later.
이런 추태를 보이긴 싫었는데
쟤 때문에 정말 복장 터지겠다
I'm so sorry you got caught
in the middle of that.
I didn't mean to be so out there,
but I am furious with him.
진정하지?
Calm down?
노력은 하는데 폭발 직전이야
I'm trying.
Man, that guy can push my buttons!
왜 그렇게 화가 났어?
Why are you so mad?
- 그 얘긴 하고 싶지 않아
- 이게 무슨...
-I don't wanna talk about it.
-lt seems like
너도 리스트에 올라가고
싶으면 계속 떠들어라
You wanna be on my list too?
Keep talking.
근데 내 리스트 못 봤니?
Has anyone seen my list, by the way?
아니, 어떻게 생겼는데?
No. What's it look like?
- '로스'라고 적힌 쪽지
- 그렇구나
-A piece of paper and it says, "Ross."
-I see.
- 얘들아
- 그래
I just got off the phone with Estelle.
Guess what?
에스텔이랑 통화했는데
뭐라는 줄 알아?
I got the lead!
나 주연 먹었다!
You got the lead in a movie?
What's it about?
주인공이야? 잘됐다
무슨 영화인데?
'셔터스피드'라고
기막힌 작품이야
It's called Shutterspeed.
It's really cool.
I meet this girl in the subway
and we fall in love in, like, a day.
지하철에서 만난 여자와
하루 만에 사랑에 빠지는데
갑자기 여자가 사라져버려
And then she disappears.
But I find out where she lives.
내가 여자의 집을 찾아가자
어떤 노파가 문을 열어주지
This old lady answers the door.
I say, "Where's Betsy?"
내가 벳시의 행방을 물으니까
그 노파가 이러는 거야
'벳시는 10년 전에 죽었수'
And she says, "Betsy's been dead
for 10 years."
우... 소름끼친다
Chilling!
The best part is, we're filming
in the desert outside of Vegas.
게다가 촬영장소는
라스베이거스 외곽의 사막이야
- 짐작이 되냐, 임마?
- 당연하지, 임마
-You know what that means.
-I know.
- 자동차 여행!
- 기분 째진다!
Road trip! We can rent a car.
I have to be there by Tuesday.
차를 빌리자
화요일까지 가면 돼
Wait! My grandmother's dead.
잠깐, 우리 할머니
돌아가셨잖아
우리 그 얘기하자
We can talk about that too, Phoebe.
그게 아니라 할머니 택시
No, her cab.
She probably won't be using it.
Drive it to Las Vegas.
할머니는 안 쓰실 테니까
너희들이 타고 가면 되지
그게 좋겠네
고맙다, 피비
All right! Thanks!
잠깐만...
그럼 내 회사는?
What are we gonna do about my job?
Not go.
나가지 마
맞아, 그렇지!
라스베이거스로 간다!
Great! Road trip, baby!
Is this okay?
그래도 되지?
챈들러, 내 허락 받을
필요 없어
Chandler, you don't have to ask
for my permission.
You can go.
- 다녀와
- 고마워
레이첼, 뭐해?
병원 갈 시간이다
Rach, we'll be late
for the eye doctor.
알았어, 까짓 거 뭐
All right. Let's get this over with.
이런, 내가 무슨 짓을 한 거야
Look what I did.
바닥이 엉망이네
청소부터 해야겠다
I mean, look at this mess.
We're gonna probably have to
clean this up.
- 어림없어
- 예약 다시 잡자
I mean, we're gonna have to reschedule!
이 정도에 흔들릴 거라고
생각했다면 오산이야
If you thought that this mess
was gonna bother me, you are wrong!
All right, let's go, Blinky.
- 가자, 안질 소녀
- 알았어
챈들러...
안녕, 조이?
Hey, Joey. What's up?
- 어서 와
- 뭐해?
라스베이거스까지
어느 길로 가야 할지 모르겠어
I can't decide which route
to take to Vegas.
You've traveled a lot, right?
잠깐, 너 여행 많이 했지?
- 했다면 좀 했지
- 좋아
Yeah, I've been around.
Which route should I take?
The north or the south route?
그럼 어느 쪽이 좋겠어
북쪽 길? 남쪽 길?
If you take the north route,
there's a man with a beard of bees.
북쪽 일리노이엔 벌떼를
수염처럼 매단 사람이 있어
Great! Problem solved!
좋았어, 고민 끝
하지만 남쪽으로 가면
삼목 두는 닭이 있는데?
On the south route, there's a chicken
that plays tic-tac-toe.
Well, back to square one.
다시 원점이잖아
I know a way that you can decide.
참, 괜찮은 방법이 있다
I'll ask you a series of questions
and you answer as quickly as you can.
좋아, 내가 질문을 하면
넌 최대한 빨리 대답해
알았어
Yes!
Good. But wait.
됐어, 지금 말고
시작할게, 긴장을 풀고...
Here we go. I want you to relax.
Take a deep breath.
숨을 깊이 들이쉬고
마음을 비워
Clear your mind.
어떤 게 좋아?
-Peanut butter or egg whites?
-Peanut butter.
- 땅콩버터? 달걀흰자?
- 땅콩버터
뭐가 되고 싶어?
-Be a fireman or a swimmer?
-Swimmer.
- 소방관? 수영선수?
- 수영선수
누구랑 자고 싶어?
모니카? 레이첼?
-You'd sleep with Monica or Rachel?
-Monica.
모니카, 오우...
I always thought it'd be Rachel.
레이첼일 줄 알았는데
-No thinking. Tie or ascot?
-Ascot.
안 돼, 생각하지 마
- 넥타이? 스카프?
- 스카프
- 북쪽 길? 남쪽 길?
- 북쪽 길
-North or south route?
-North.
짠! 답 나왔지?
Bam! There you go! Huh?
진짜 신기하다
That was incredible!
Beard of bees here I come!
땡벌털보야, 내가 간다
얘들아
This guy again.
저 화상 또 왔네
Hey, what's up?
- 안녕?
- 그래, 별일 없지?
Not much. Wanna see a movie tonight?
그럼, 오늘밤에 영화나 볼까?
What do you wanna see?
- 좋아, 뭘 볼 건데?
- 글쎄...
I don't know.
그럴 땐 방법이 있지
피비, 아까 그거 해봐
I know how to decide.
Show him your game.
음... 됐네요
No, thank you.
What's with her?
왜 저러니?
I don't know.
I know how we can decide.
난들 아나
그냥 내가 해볼게
I'm gonna ask you questions
and you answer real quick.
지금부터 내 질문에
최대한 빨리 대답해
알았어
뭐가 좋아?
-Action or comedy?
-Action.
- 액션? 코미디?
- 액션
누구랑 잘래?
모니카? 레이첼?
Who would you rather sleep with,
Monica or Rachel?
Dude, you are sick.
너 어디 아프냐?
미안, 레이첼이랑
그렇고 그랬었지?
I'm sorry. I forgot you had
that whole Rachel thing.
Oh, my God. What does that thing do?
맙소사, 이건 또 뭐야?
-An eye removal machine.
-I'm out of here.
눈알 뽑는 기계래
- 됐어, 난 갈래
- 농담이야, 농담
I'm kidding.
Rachel, I'm Dr. Miller.
어서 와요, 레이첼
닥터 밀러예요
Monica said you were nervous.
Everything will be fine.
모니카한테 얘기 들었는데
걱정할 거 하나도 없어요
그럼 가도 되죠?
-So we're done.
-Almost, but first we gotta start.
금방 끝납니다
진찰부터 하죠
This is a glaucoma test. Sit down.
녹내장 테스트예요
앉으시죠
그러죠
여기 턱을 대시고
Put your chin here.
Now, you'll feel a small puff of air
in each eye.
이제 양쪽 눈에
바람을 불겠어요
뭐라구요?
What?
A small puff of air.
Now, come on!
바람이래잖아, 빨리 대!
- 시작합니다
- 좋아요
Here we go.
One, two, three.
하나, 둘, 셋
죄송해요, 됐어요
I'm sorry. All right.
이번엔 가만있을게요
좋아요
I'm gonna stay in here this time.
준비됐죠?
Ready?
하나, 둘...
-One, two
-I'm sorry.
죄송해요
You know what?
I'm gonna hold her head.
제가 머리를 잡고 있을게요
됐습니다
That's okay.
- 알았어요
- 네
하세요
하나...
둘...
I'm sorry.
죄송해요
관둡시다, 젊으니까
녹내장은 아닐 거예요
You're young.
You don't have glaucoma.
야호!
- 정말 반가웠어요, 선생님
- 어디 볼까요?
So it was very, very nice
to meet you, sir.
악! 무슨 짓이에요
정신 나갔어요?
What are you?
Are you crazy?
좋습니다, 좌측 눈에
염증이 약간 있군요
You got a small, minor infection
in that left eye.
Take these drops for a week
and you'll be as good as new.
이 안약을 1일 3회씩 한 주만
넣어주면 말끔히 나을 겁니다
전 눈에 그런 거 안 넣어요
No, I don't put things in my eye.
We'll see you here in three months.
And I'll fit you for a glass eye.
그럼 좋아요
3개월 후에 봅시다
- 좋아요
- 유리 눈을 끼워드리죠
그거 당장 이리 내놔요
Give me the damn drops!
밀러 박사님?
Dr. Miller?
P, E, C, F, D
P-E-C-F-D.
참 잘했어요, 모니카
Very good, Monica!
- 어디 있는지 알죠?
- 그럼요
-You know where they are.
-I sure do.
- 넌 사탕 못 받았지?
- 됐다 얘
And you don't get one.
그 안약 신통하더라
눈병이 싹 나았어
You know, those eye drops
are a miracle.
My eye is 100 percent better.
- 아직 내 주머니에 있어
- 빌어먹을!
-They're still in my coat.
-Damn!
얘들아
다 준비했어?
You ready to go?
거기 많이 춥냐? 코트 말고
이 조끼 한 보따리면 될까?
How cold will it be there?
Will all these sweater vests be enough?
왜?
-What?
-I love you.
사랑해
로스도 가면 좋을 텐데
보고 싶을 거야
I wish Ross was coming with us.
I'll miss him.
Thanks. I just got
that jerk out of my mind.
그 화상 잊을 만하니까
또 들먹이고 앉았네
어디서 묵을 거야?
대형호텔 특실인가?
Is the movie putting us up
in a big hotel suite?
아니, 독립영화라 예산이 부족해
난 네 방에서 지낼까 했는데
Not really.
It's an independent film.
We don't have a big budget.
I'll stay in your room.
출연료 받으면 특실로 가자
주인공이니까 많이 받겠지?
Once you get paid,
you'll be springing for a suite.
They must be paying you a lot.
이건 어때?
For every dollar Shutterspeed makes...
이 영화 수익금 1달러 당
1페니는 조이 주머니로 들어와
...one penny of it goes
right in Joey's pocket.
영화가 망하면
너도 개털 된다고?
You don't get paid unless
it makes money?
Did you not hear the plot
of the movie?
영화 줄거리 못 들었냐?
"She's been dead for 10 years."
'걔는 10년 전에 죽었수'
벼락부자 되는 거야
I'm gonna be a millionaire!
- 얘들아
- 그래
- 인사하려고 들렀어
- 잘 왔다
I wanted to say goodbye.
And to see if you guys would
place a little bet for me.
그리고 나 대신 돈 좀 걸어줘
Twenty bucks on black 15.
블랙 15에 20달러
- 아무렴
- 좋아
-You got it!
-All right.
-You remember the number, right?
-Yeah, black 13.
번호 까먹지 마
- 그래, 블랙 13
- 블랙 15!
-Black 15!
-You got it.
- 알았어
- 그렇지
-All right. Bye-bye, now.
-Bye, you guys.
- 그럼 잘 있어
- 안녕, 잘 다녀와
- 차까지 배웅해줄게
- 좋지
I'll say bye at the car.
Anyone wanna say bye to me
at the car?
나 배웅해줄 사람은 없냐?
내가 차까지 배웅할게
눈곱 낀 애도 괜찮다면
I'll say goodbye to you at the car
if you don't mind the pus.
See you!
또 보자
But wait a minute. The pus is good.
It means it's healing.
왜 그래, 눈곱 끼면
다 나았다는 거야
피비, 뭐 읽어?
Hey, Phoebe. What you reading?
피비?
여보세요?
Hello?
피비?
피비...
피... 피비
Come on!
너 왜 이래!
미안, 너 거기 있었어?
Sorry, I didn't see you there.
Phoebe, are you mad at me
or something?
혹시 나한테 화나는 거 있니?
뭘 잘못했는지 얘기를 해봐
If you are, please tell me
what it is I did.
-lf you don't know, I can't help you.
-I don't know.
본인도 모르는데
난들 어쩌겠어
- 난 모르는데?
- 난들 어쩌겠어
Well, I can't help you.
뭔지는 모르겠지만
내가 잘못했어, 됐니?
Well, whatever it is,
I am very, very sorry. Okay?
Apology accepted.
사과 받아줄게
알았어
So we're good?
그럼 이제 된 거지?
좋아
그럼 나중에 보자
I'll see you later, okay?
잘 가라, 짝궁뎅이
Bye, fat-ass.
뭐야!
All right!
Will you please tell me what it is
that made you so mad at me?
대체 왜 화가 났는지
말을 해야 알 거 아냐
나도 몰라, 기억 안 나
I don't know! I don't remember!
What do you mean, you can't remember?
뭐? 기억이 안 나다니
그런 게 어디 있어?
너무 화가 나서
왜 화가 났는지 잊어버렸어
I was so focused on being mad at you,
I forgot what it was I was mad about.
If you can't remember,
can't we just forget about this?
기억도 안 나는 일인데
그냥 잊어버리면 안 돼?
안 되지, 너한테 화난 건
확실히 기억하니까
Oh, no. I am mad at you.
I know that much.
But I'm sorry about the fat-ass thing
because you have a sweet, little heinie.
짝궁뎅이라고 한 건 미안해
사실 네 엉덩이 무지 귀여워
이런, 슬슬 피곤해지는데
조금 있다가 자리 바꾸자
I'm getting pretty tired.
You'll have to take over soon.
출발한 지 30분밖에 안 됐어
We've been driving for a half-hour.
You haven't looked at the road once.
길 한 번이나 쳐다봤냐?
뻔한 길 봐서 뭐해
Don't worry. It's out there.
Maybe I just need lunch.
You wanna eat?
- 점심을 걸러서 그런가?
- 그래
너도 먹을래?
My treat.
내가 사지
그거 로스 돈 아냐?
Isn't that Ross' money?
그래, 좋아
Ross' treat.
Where do you wanna eat?
로스가 낸다
- 어디서 먹을까?
- 글쎄
I don't know.
그럴 땐 좋은 방법이 있어
I know how we can decide.
I'll ask you questions.
지금부터 내가 하는 질문에
넌 최대한 빨리 대답해
And then you have to answer real fast.
마음을 비워, 깨끗하게
So clear your mind.
Clear it right out. Clear it out.
- 텅 비우는 거야
- 알았어
It's all clear except for this image
of a small, purple lamp.
다 사라졌어, 조그만
자주색 램프만 빼고
그건 있어도 되냐?
Is that all right if that stays in there?
- 당연하지
- 안 될 거 있나
I don't see why not. I guess.
You have to answer with the first thing
that pops into your head, okay?
맨 먼저 떠오르는 걸 말해
- 그래
- 좋아...
-Would you rather be too wet or too dry?
-Too dry.
- 젖은 게 좋아? 마른 게 좋아?
- 마른 거
- 귀신을 믿니? 네, 아니오로
- 아니오
-Do you believe in ghosts?
-No.
-Will this movie be my big break?
- 나 이번에 뜨겠냐?
- 아니
-What?
-Yes.
뭐?
네
-Dude, you said, no.
-I also said, yes.
- 방금 아니라면서
- 다시 '네'라고 했어
이번에 나 뜰 것 같지 않아?
-This won't be my big break?
-No.
아니, 허걱!
I don't believe this.
진짜 너무한다
Look, I just don't want you to get
your hopes up too high.
조이, 그러니까...
너무 큰 기대는 갖지 마
그게 무슨 소리야?
난 이 영화의 주인공이야
What are you talking about?
I'm the lead in a movie!
돈 한 푼 못 받은 주인공?
They're not even paying you!
This doesn't sound like a real movie!
이 영화 찍긴 찍는 거냐?
그만둬라, 모처럼 찾아온
행운을 깎아 내리고 앉았네
I don't know why you're dumping
all over my big break.
이런 걸로 성공하긴 힘들어
I don't think this is gonna be
your big break.
그래서 따라나섰냐?
내 기분 잡치려고?
Are you on this trip
to make me feel like a loser?
-I'd rather be alone.
-You don't want me here?
그럼 그렇다고 해
혼자 갈 테니까
- 내렸으면 좋겠냐?
- 계속 그렇게 나올 거면
Not if you're like this.
The next time you ask me
a question like that, I'll lie.
다음에 그런 거 물어보면
거짓말해줄게
I don't want you on the trip.
그래, 같이 가기 싫다
Why don't you pull over.
I'll get out now.
알았어, 차 세워
당장 내릴 테니까
Fine.
좋지
Get out.
내려
You can't stop on a bridge.
그렇다고 다리 중간에서
세우면 어떡하냐
- 내려!
- 알았어!
-Get out!
-Fine!
Wait! Wait! There's no sidewalk!
잠깐, 여긴 인도도 없어
Yeah. I'm gonna die here.
그래, 난 이제 죽었다
Are you mad at me
because my hair gel smells?
내 헤어젤 냄새 때문에 화났니?
아니
Because I said your handwriting
is childlike?
네가 글씨를 어린애처럼
쓴다고 해서 화났니?
No. That made me feel precious.
아니, 그땐 뿌듯했어
Because he's always
correcting people's grammar?
알았다, 오빤 틈만 나면
남들 문법 교정하잖아
"Whom, whom." Sometimes it's "who"!
whom, whom...
who가 맞을 때도 있어
Yeah? Sometimes it's:
가끔은 이게 맞지
Did you beat him at a board game?
He's such a baby when he loses.
보드게임에서 지니까
얘가 치사하게 나오든?
Okay, I'm the baby.
그래, 나 치사하다
Hey! Stop it!
하지 마!
나 왔다
What are you doing here?
챈들러, 어떻게 된 거야?
Joey kicked me out of the car
on the bridge.
조이가 조지 워싱턴 다리에
날 버리고 갔다
-Why?
-I don't know. He went crazy.
왜?
갑자기 열을 내잖아
We played that game where you
ask questions and answer fast.
둘이서 게임을 했거든
빨리 대답하는 거 있잖아
That game should not be played
without my supervision.
내 감독도 없이
그 게임을 하다니
I don't know what made him mad.
도대체 영문을 모르겠어
All I said was that
this wouldn't be his big break...
이번에 뜨기 힘들겠다고
말한 것뿐인데
...that it wouldn't do
anything for him...
큰 기대는 하지 말라고
...and that it didn't sound real.
같지도 않은 영화라고
Okay, he should've
pushed me off the bridge.
그래, 다리 밑으로
안 떨어진 게 다행이다
What's in the bag?
손에 든 건 뭐야?
I figured you'd be mad at me...
너희들한테 혼날 것 같아서
도로변에서 선물 좀 주워왔어
...so I got gifts that I found
on the roadside.
-Who wants the one-legged teddy bear?
-I do!
다리 하나 떨어진
곰 인형 가질 사람
나
좋아
-Not even close.
-I need help! I can't do this.
- 근처에도 안 갔어
- 그럼 나 좀 도와줘
- 혼자선 못하겠어
- 알았어, 이리 와
Come on. Let's do it.
- 자, 여기 앉아
- 알았어
Sit down.
All right, put your head back.
- 됐지? 고개 젖히고
- 좋아
-Now open your eyes.
-Okay, they are.
- 눈 크게 떠
- 알았어, 자
-How many fingers am I holding up?
-Four.
- 내가 손가락 몇 개 폈지?
- 네 개
I was thinking four.
세상에, 나도 네 개 생각했는데
-Really?
-Yes!
- 진짜?
- 그래
Why don't we start
with a practice one.
안 되겠다
연습부터 해보자
알았어
-No drops.
-Great!
- 약은 안 넣을게
- 좋아
- 셋을 센다
- 그래
On three. One, two, three.
하나, 둘, 셋
My pillow's all wet!
쿠션 젖었잖아
Well, you said it was practice!
뭐, 연습이라면서
Why did you move?
- 근데 왜 피해?
- 거짓말인 줄 알았으니까
I knew you were lying!
- 자, 이리 와
- 뭐하는 거야?
-Come here.
-What are you doing?
- 모니카, 하지 마!
- 까불지 말고
Stop it! Oh, my God!
하지 마
I am going....
안 뒤집어?
Turn it over!
I am going to get...
이걸 네 눈에
꼭 넣고 말겠어
...get these drops in your eye.
너 정말 왜 이렇게
힘이 세니
Oh, my God! You really are
freakishly strong.
그만! 그만!
모니카, 그만해!
Stop! Stop!
Stop it!
Damn, it's empty!
젠장, 다 나왔어!
If Joey and Chandler walked in now,
we could make a fortune.
조이랑 챈들러가 봤으면
우린 큰돈 버는 건데
That is definitely Chandler,
Joey or Ross.
우! 챈들러 아니면
조이 아니면 로스다
Or Rachel.
아니면 레이첼이든지
여보세요?
It's Joey.
- 조이야
- 거봐
전화 잘했다, 그러고 와서
챈들러도 편치 않은가 봐
Chandler told me what happened.
He's really upset.
Not as upset as he'll be when he finds
out what I did with his sweater vests.
조끼가 어떻게 됐는지 알면
아마 더 불편해질 걸
What did you do to them?
조끼를 어떻게 했는데?
There's a well-dressed
pack of dogs in Ohio.
오하이오엔 잘 차려입은
개들이 많다고만 말해두지
모니카, 피비 거기 있니?
차에 대해 물어볼 게 있어
I gotta ask Phoebe
something about the car.
Hold on one second.
그래, 잠깐만 기다려
-Hey, dude.
-Hey, Phoebe.
- 전화 바꿨네
- 안녕, 피비
좌석 밑에 나무상자가
하나 있던데 이게 뭐지?
This wooden box keeps sliding out.
What is it?
My grandma.
우리 할머니야
And thanks.
She's having a great time.
고맙다, 조이
할머니도 즐거우실 거야
조이야? 조이면 나 좀 바꿔
Is that Joey? Let me talk to him.
조이? 챈들러가 너한테...
Chandler's here.
He was wondering if
I guess he ran out of change.
동전이 떨어졌나 봐
How am I gonna apologize to him
if he won't even talk to me?
날 상대도 안 해주는데
무슨 수로 사과를 하지?
Send him something. So when he
gets there, he'll know you're sorry.
선물을 보내면 어떨까?
라스베이거스에 도착하면
받아볼 수 있도록
That's a good idea. I wonder where
I could get a basket of porn?
그게 좋겠네
포르노 한 바구니는
어디서 주문하지?
- 포르노로 사과하는 게 어딨어?
- 안 돼?
No, don't say, "I'm sorry," with porn.
You should send him
a carton of cigarettes.
담배 한 보루를 보내는 거야
담배는 상납금으로 쓸 수 있거든
Because that way he can trade it
for protection.
아니, 그건 감옥 얘기다
No. That's prison.
좋아, 피비
해결방법이 있어
I know how we're gonna
figure this out.
마음을 비우고 내 질문에
맨 처음 생각나는 걸 대답해
Clear your mind...
...and answer the first thing
that comes into your head.
- 뭐가 좋아? 식물? 동물?
- 동물
-Do you like flora or fauna?
-Fauna.
누가 되고 싶어?
사이먼? 가펑클?
-Simon or Garfunkel?
-Garfunkel.
가펑클
-Why are you mad?
-You said I was boring.
- 왜 나한테 화났어?
- 날더러 따분한 인간이래서
When did I say that?
내가 언제 따분하다고 했어
맞아, 이제 기억난다
우리가 체스 할 때
Oh, my God! I remember now!
We were playing chess.
Phoebe, you and l
have never played chess.
피비, 너랑 난
체스 한 적이 없어
무슨 소리야, 얼음 호수에서
체스 하다 내가 따분하댔잖아
Remember that time on the frozen lake?
We were playing. You said I was boring.
Then you took off your energy mask
and you were Cameron Diaz.
그러다 영양 팩 뜯어내니까
너 카메론 디아즈더라고
어쩜 꿈이었는지도 모르겠다
There's a chance this
may have been a dream.
So this entire time, you've been
angry with me because of a dream?
그니까 지금까지 나한테
화를 낸 게 꿈 때문이었다고?
Well, guess what, now I'm mad at you.
이제 내가 너한테 화난다
아야!
I wanted to make sure this wasn't a dream.
이것도 생시가 아니라면
시간낭비만 하는 거야
Otherwise we're wasting our time.
감독님! 저 왔어요
Stanley!
주인공 도착했습니다
작업 시작해야죠?
Your leading man is here.
Let's get to work.
계획에 차질이 좀 생겼어
간판 내렸네
Slight change of plans.
We've shut down.
네? 왜요?
What? Why?
It's a money thing.
We don't have any.
돈이지 뭐, 거덜났어
You're kidding, right?
농담이죠?
- 아니
- 네?
What?
오래가진 않을 거야
It's probably just temporary.
We're hoping to get some money soon.
Just hang out.
돈줄을 찾는 중이니까
잠시만 대기하고 있어
대기라뇨
언제까지요?
Hang out? How long?
I don't know. A week. Maybe two.
The money will turn up.
글쎄, 1주나 2주?
돈은 곧 들어와
투자가는 줄을 섰으니까
이봐, 자네 돈 좀 있나?
People always wanna invest in movies.
You're not rich?
- 없어요
- 한번 물어봤어
Worth a shot.
Well, Joey, let me know
where you're staying, okay?
조이, 숙소 정하면 연락하라고
Hey, pal. Are you Joey Tribbiani?
- 보쇼, 댁이 조이 트리비아니요?
- 네
이게 왔더군요
These got left for you.
고마워요
Thanks.
"Congratulations on your big break."
'이번에 확실히 뜨는 거야'
여보세요?
- 모니카, 나 조이야
- 안녕, 조이?
-Monica, it's Joey.
-Hey, Joey.
You remember me
even though you're a star.
인기스타께서
날 다 기억해주고
Come on. It'll be years
before I forget you.
무슨 소리, 널 잊으려면
몇 년은 걸릴 거야
What's it like on a movie set?
촬영장 분위기 어때?
Do you have a dressing room
and a chair with your name?
네 이름이 적힌 의자에
전용분장실도 있겠네?
그야 기본이지 뭐
그건 그렇고...
Yeah, yeah, I got all that going on.
챈들러한테 상황파악
잘하라고 꼭 전해줘
Tell Chandler he couldn't
have been more wrong.
이만 끊어야겠다
내 초밥이 왔어
I gotta go, Monica. My sushi's here.
기다리시게 해서 죄송합니다
Sorry about that.
Thanks for waiting.
모두 웃으세요
Everybody smile.
됐습니다
감사합니다
Thanks a lot. Enjoy your stay
at Caesars. We hope it's toga-rific.
시저스 팰리스에서 짜릿한
시간 보내시기 바랍니다
내가 혀를 깨물고 죽어야지
Kill me. Kill me now.
Rach, can you pass me the TV Guide?
- 레이첼, TV 가이드 좀 줄래?
- 그래
Go!
잡아!
뭐하는 짓이야!
이거 놔!
What are you doing?
Get off! Oh, my God!
- 엄마야!
- 눈 벌리고 있어
Hold it open. Okay.
We'll see you in about
three or four hours.
서너 시간 후에 다시 보자